[
    {
        "name": "Buster Sword",
        "description": "The Buster Sword is an enormous broadsword. From tip to handle, it is approximately five to six feet long, with a single-edged large blade approximately one foot wide\nDeals 10 damage",
        "attack": 10,
        "move": " used Focused Thrust",
        "win_front": " used braver and smashed ",
        "win_back": " into the ground"
    },
    {
        "name": "Master Sword",
        "description": "The Master Sword is a divine magic sword with the power to vanquish evil. Infused with the sacred flames provided by the Golden Goddesses and blessed with Hylia's power\nDeals 10 damage",
        "attack": 10,
        "move": " used Sword beam",
        "win_front": " used the power of the triforce to vanquish ",
        "win_back": " from the face of the earth"
    },
    {
        "name": "Leviathan Axe",
        "description": "The Leviathan axe legendary two-handed battle axe imbued with elemental magic allowing it to return to the user\nDeals 40 damage",
        "attack": 40,
        "move": " threw the Leviathan Axe",
        "win_front": " lunged towards ",
        "win_back": " and decapitated it"
    },
    {
        "name": "Portal Gun",
        "description": "The Portal Gun is a hand-held device which has the ability to manufacture two linked portals. No matter the distance between them, any object which passes through one portal will emerge from the other and vice versa instantaneously\nDeals 40 damage",
        "attack": 40,
        "move": " used portals",
        "win_front": " used a portal to send ",
        "win_back": " to the moon"
    },
    {
        "name": "Virtuous Treaty",
        "description": "The Virtuous Treaty is a pure white samurai blade not sullied by a single drop of blood\nDeals 50 damage",
        "attack": 50,
        "move": " used Virtuous Treaty",
        "win_front": " struck ",
        "win_back": " down in one clean slash"
    },
    {
        "name": "Coronacht",
        "description": "The Coronacht is an infernal arm, the finest bow ever conceived, once wielded by Mistress Hera\nDeals 60 damage",
        "attack": 60,
        "move": " used power shot",
        "win_front": " used the aspect of Hera to shoot a power shot right through ",
        "win_back": ""
    },
    {
        "name": "Zenith",
        "description": "The Zenith is a legendary blade crafted using 10 different powerful swords\nDeals 70 damage",
        "attack": 70,
        "move": " used The Zenith",
        "win_front": " obliterated ",
        "win_back": " using the power of 10 swords"
    },
    {
        "name": "RGX Butterfly Knife",
        "description": "The RGX Butterfly Knife is the most powerful butterfly knife on earth due to its RGB\nDeals 60 damage",
        "attack": 60,
        "move": " used behind the 8 ball",
        "win_front": " performed the valorant inspect flawlessly causing ",
        "win_back": " to self destruct"
    },
    {
        "name": "Elder Wand",
        "description": "The most powerful wand on earth",
        "attack": 10,
        "move": "",
        "win_front": "",
        "win_back": ""
    },
    {
        "name": "Wand",
        "description": "A generic wand\nDeals 5 damage",
        "attack": 5,
        "move": " threw the wand",
        "win_front": " poked ",
        "win_back": " to death"
    },
    {
        "name": "Marksman Revolver",
        "description": "A revolver. Every few seconds a coin pops out of the bottom of the gun. The purpose of this function is lost on you\nDeals 50 damage",
        "attack": 50,
        "move": " used +HEADSHOT",
        "win_front": " threw $4.32 of change at ",
        "win_back": ", knocking it out"
    },
    {
        "name": "Toy Knife",
        "description": "Made of plastic. A rarity nowadays\nDeals 1 damage",
        "attack": 1,
        "move": " used stab",
        "win_front": " stabbed ",
        "win_back": " so much it died"
    },
    {
        "name": "X Baton",
        "description": "The X Baton is a police baton capable of transforming between three different styles, each with their own unique abilities and merits\nDeals 100 damage",
        "attack": 100,
        "move": " used blaster mode",
        "win_front": " activated Gladius Mode and decimated ",
        "win_back": ""
    }
]
